Register of the David Starr Jordan Papers, 1794-1950
Hoover Institution Archives
- CORRESPONDENCE, 1873-1932
  - McNary, Charles L., 1919-1920 (Folder 27)
  - Mead, Edwin D., 1910-1931 (Folder 28-32)
  - Mead, Lucia Ames, 1912-1929 (Folder 33)
  - Mears, Eliot G., 1921 (Folder 34)
  - Medina, Frank P., 1911 (Folder 35)
  - Meiklejohn, Alexander, 1914 (Folder 36)
  - Meldrum, Herbert A., 1914 (Box 73, Folder 1)
  - Mendelson, Walter, 1915 (Folder 2)
  - Merkel, O. J., 1915 (Folder 3)
  - Merton, S. D., 1921 (Folder 4)
  - Messenger, 1919 (Folder 5)
  - Mexican-American League, 1916 (Folder 6)
  - Mez, John, 1913-1931 (Folder 7-11)
  - Michel, O. J., 1915 (Folder 12)
  - Mickey, J. L., 1913 (Folder 13)
  - Mighels, Ella S., 1914-1915 (Folder 14)
  - Miles, Sherman, 1914 (Folder 15)
  - Milholland, John, 1920-1921 (Folder 16)
  - Miller, A. C., 1914 (Folder 17)
  - Miller, Arthur, 1920-1923 (Folder 18)
  - Miller, Frank A., 1911-1929 (Folder 19)
  - Miller, George J., 1915-1925 (Folder 20)
  - Miller, Jacob M., 1916-1918 (Folder 21)
  - Miller, Joaquin (Cincinnatus Hiner), 1896 (Folder 22)
  - Miller, S. A., 1913-1914 (Folder 23)
  - Miller, Stephen I., 1912 (Folder 24)
  - Miller, William B., 1915 (Folder 25)
  - Mills, John N., 1915 (Folder 26)
  - Milne, A., 1913-1929 (Folder 27)
  - Milwaukee Journal, 1916-1917 (Folder 28)
  - Minder, E.F., 1914 (Folder 29)
  - Minnesota School for Feeble-Minded and Colony for Epileptics, 1912 (Folder 30)
  - Mischendorf, George H., 1915 (Folder 31)
  - Misrow, Joyesh C., 1923 (Folder 32)
  - Misu, G., 1915-1919 (Folder 33)
  - Mitchell, J. L., 1891 (Folder 34)
  - Mitchell, M. J., 1914 (Folder 35)
  - Mitchell, S. C., 1912 (Folder 36)
  - Miyakawa, Masuji, 1913 (Folder 37)
  - Mlynarski, Felix J., 1916 (Box 74, Folder 1)
  - Moch, Gaston, 1910-1913 (Folder 2)
  - Moffat, Yard and Company, 1911 (Folder 3)
  - Moffitt, E. E., Mrs., 1914 (Folder 4)
  - Mohn, Anton, 1915 (Folder 5)
  - Monitor, 1899 (Folder 6)
  - Monroe, Paul, 1912 (Folder 7)
  - Moon, Newman, 1917 (Folder 8)
  - Mooney, Tom, 1927-1928 (Folder 9)
  - Moore, Bruce, 1913 (Folder 10)
  - Moran, H. A., 1913-1916 (Folder 11)
  - Morgan, T. M., 1916 (Folder 12)
  - Morgenthau, Henry, 1919 (Folder 13)
  - Moritzen, Julius, 1912 (Folder 14)
  - Morse-Stephens, Henry, 1916 (Folder 15)
  - Moscheles, Felix, 1913-1914 (Folder 16)
  - Mosely, Alfred, 1914 (Folder 17)
  - Moses, Eaton L., 1915 (Folder 18)
  - Mosher, C. D., 1918 (Folder 19)
  - Mott, John R., 1910-1916 (Folder 20)
  - Muller, Arthur, 1913-1921 (Folder 21)
  - Muller, Ida, 1919-1931 (Folder 22)
  - Mullowney, John, 1916 (Folder 23)
  - Murphey, Starr J., 1911 (Folder 24)
  - Murphy, Charles T., 1921 (Folder 25)
  - Murphy, Robert Cushman, 1914 (Folder 26)
  - Murray, A. T., 1912 (Folder 27)
  - Murray, Gilbert, 1922 (Folder 28)
  - Murrow, Ed R., 1930 (Folder 29)
  - Musée Royal d'Histoire Naturelle de Belgique, 1913 (Folder 30)
  - Mussey, Henry S., 1920-1928 (Folder 31)
  - Muzzey, David S., 1918-1928 (Folder 32)
  - Myer, A. N., 1914 (Folder 33)
  - Myers, Denys P., 1911-1916 (Folder 34)
  - Nagai, Matsuzo, 1911-1912 (Folder 35)
  - Nagel, Charles, 1912 (Folder 36)
  - Naiad, Nicholas, 1927 (Folder 37)
  - Nasmyth, George W., Mrs., 1911-1916 (Folder 38)
  - Nation (London), 1915-1925 (Folder 39)
  - Nation (New York), 1918-1928 (Folder 39A)
  - National Allied Relief Committee, 1915 (Folder 40)
  - National Association for the Advancement of Colored People, 1919-1921 (Folder 41)
  - National Citizens Union, 1917 (Folder 42)
  - National Civil Liberties Bureau, 1919 (Folder 43)
  - National Committee on American Japanese Relations, 1924 (Folder 44)
  - National Conference on Lynching, 1919 (Folder 45)
  - National Conservation Congress, 1914 (Folder 46)
  - National Council for the Prevention of War, 1923-1931 (Folder 47)
  - National Economic League, 1918 (Folder 48)
  - National Education Association, 1913-1929 (Folder 49)
  - National Industrial Peace Association, 1911 (Folder 50)
  - National Motion Picture League, 1927 (Folder 51)
  - National News Bureau, 1914 (Folder 52)
  - National Peace Council, London, 1913 (Folder 53)
  - National Peace Council, New Zealand, 1913-1925 (Folder 54)
  - National Reclamation Association, 1913 (Folder 55)
  - National Reform Association, 1912 (Folder 56)
  - National Student Committee for the Limitation of Armaments, 1922 (Folder 57)
  - Navy, 1913 (Folder 58)
  - Near East Relief, 1919-1923 (Box 75, Folder 1)
  - Nearing, Scott, 1923 (Folder 2)
  - Nebraska Peace Society, 1913 (Folder 3)
  - Nederlandsch Onderwijzers-Genootschap, 1915 (Folder 4)
  - Nederlandsche Anti-Oorlog Raad, 1914 (Folder 5)
  - Nelson, Lars P., 1914 (Folder 6)
  - New, Harry S., 1919 (Folder 7)
  - New Appeal, 1919 (Folder 8)
  - New Day, 1921 (Folder 9)
  - New Mexico Educational Association, 1912 (Folder 10)
  - New Republic, 1916-1928 (Folder 11)
  - New York Evening Mail, 1916 (Folder 12)
  - New York Peace Society, 1912-1914 (Folder 13)
  - New York Times, 1914 (Folder 14)
  - Newcomer, Carrie E., 1893 (Folder 15)
  - Newlander, C.W., 1914-1915 (Folder 16)
  - Newman, Jared T., 1914-1915 (Folder 17)
  - Ng Poon Chew, 1912-1920 (Folder 18)
  - Nibley, Joel, 1913-1928 (Folder 19)
  - Nichols, Ernest Fox, 1914-1915 (Folder 20)
  - Nielsen, Carl H., 1913 (Folder 21)
  - Nielsen, Julia A., 1911 (Folder 22)
  - Nieto, Jacob, 1911 (Folder 23)
  - Nobel Prize Committee, 1919-1923 (Folder 24)
  - Noguchi, Y., 1897 (Folder 25)
  - Norris, George W., 1921-1928 (Folder 26)
  - Norris, Kathleen, 1927 (Folder 27)
  - Northern California Indian Association, 1916 (Folder 28)
  - Northwestern State Normal School, 1911 (Folder 29)
  - Novicow, J., 1910-1912 (Folder 30)
  - Noyes, Alfred, 1916 (Folder 31)
  - Noyes, William A., 1927-1929 (Folder 32)
  - Nunan, C. R., 1912 (Folder 33)
  - Nyi, Z. T., 1913 (Folder 34)
  - Oehme, Robert, 1910-1911 (Folder 35)
  - O'Halloran, Thomas, 1913 (Folder 36)
  - Okuma, S., 1915 (Folder 37)
  - Older, Fremont, 1901-1923 (Folder 38)
  - Oliviera Lima, M. de, 1914 (Folder 39)
  - O'Neil, James, 1915-1928 (Folder 40)
  - Oppenheim, L., 1913-1919 (Folder 41)
  - Organisation Centrale pour une Paix Durable, 1917 (Folder 42)
  - Orton, Jesse F., 1915 (Folder 43)
  - Osborne, Henry Z., 1917 (Folder 44)
  - Osgood, Wilfred H. (?), 1914 (Folder 45)
  - Osler, William, 1913 (Folder 46)
  - Oster (?), Ch., 1910-1916 (Folder 47)
  - Ostwald, Wilhelm, 1911-1913 (Folder 48)
  - O'Sullivan, Sylvester M., 1914 (Folder 49)
  - Otaki, K., 1896 (Folder 50)
  - Otlet, Paul, 1914-1928 (Folder 51)
  - Otto, P., 1914 (Folder 52)
  - Outlook, 1899 (Folder 53)
  - Owen, Robert L., 1920-1925 (Folder 54)
  - Owston, Alan, 1912-1915 (Folder 55)
  - Pachnicke, 1913 (Folder 56)
  - Page, Carroll I., 1921 (Folder 57)
  - Page, Kirby, 1926-1928 (Folder 58)
  - Palmer, Albert W., 1915 (Folder 59)
  - Pan-Pacific Union, 1921-1929 (Folder 60)
  - Panama-Pacific International Exposition, 1913-1916 (Folder 61)
  - Panaretoff, S., 1916-1922 (Folder 62)
  - Paramount Pictures, 1916 (Folder 63)
  - Park, Alice, 1921 (Folder 64)
  - Park, Robert E., 1923 (Folder 65)
  - Parker, Alton B., 1916 (Folder 66)
  - Parker, Gilbert, 1914-1915 (Folder 67)
  - Parker, J. C., 1914-1915 (Folder 68)
  - Parsons, Cassen F., 1916 (Box 76, Folder 1)
  - Passmore, Irvin, 1912 (Folder 2)
  - Patterson, John, 1915 (Folder 3)
  - Patterson, LaFayette L., 1929 (Folder 4)
  - Peabody, George Foster, 1915-1924 (Folder 5)
  - Peace and Arbitration Society of Buffalo, N.Y., 1911-1914 (Folder 6)
  - Peace Bureau, 1912 (Folder 7)
  - Peace Society, 1914 (Folder 8)
  - Peace Society of America, 1914 (Folder 9)
  - Pearse, A. S., 1922 (Folder 10)
  - Pearson, Mary S., 1913 (Folder 11)
  - Pedersen, Sigurd, 1914 (Folder 12)
  - Pélissier, Jean, 1912-1919 (Folder 13)
  - Pellegrin, Jacques, 1917-1923 (Folder 14)
  - Penniman, A. W., 1917 (Folder 15)
  - Pennsylvania Arbitration and Peace Society, 1912 (Folder 16)
  - Penrose, Boies, 1917 (Folder 17)
  - People's Council of America, 1917 (Folder 18)
  - People's Lobby, 1928 (Folder 19)
  - Perkins, George C., 1912 (Folder 20)
  - Permanent Blind Relief Fund, 1916-1919 (Folder 21)
  - Perris, G. H., 1910-1913 (Folder 22)
  - Persia. Legation (United States), 1912 (Folder 23)
  - Petavel, J. W., 1918-1927 (Folder 24)
  - Peterson, W., 1914 (Folder 25)
  - Pethick-Lawrence, F.W., 1915-1919 (Folder 26)
  - Phelan, James D., 1913-1926 (Folder 27)
  - Phelps, Byron, 1911 (Folder 28)
  - Phillips, John C., 1929 (Folder 29)
  - Phillips, John S., 1910-1911 (Folder 30)
  - Pickering, Lee Roy, 1916-1924 (Folder 31)
  - Pierce, Henry F., 1915 (Folder 32)
  - Pillsbury, Albert E., 1916-1921 (Folder 33)
  - Pinchot, Amos, 1917 (Folder 34)
  - Pinchot, Gifford, 1920-1929 (Folder 35)
  - Pinther, Theodore, 1915 (Folder 36)
  - Pittman, Key, 1919 (Folder 37)
  - Plecher, Andrew, 1915-1919 (Folder 38)
  - Plimpton, G. A., 1912-1916 (Folder 39)
  - Plummer, O. M., 1915 (Folder 40)
  - Poche, Franz, 1915 (Folder 41)
  - Pogue, John F., 1914 (Folder 42)
  - Poindexter, Miles, 1919 (Folder 43)
  - Porter, Anna, 1917-1918 (Folder 44)
  - Potrero Women's Club, 1914 (Folder 45)
  - Poulton, E. B., 1914-1915 (Folder 46)
  - Pound, Ezra, 1928-1930 (Folder 47)
  - Pounds, Marion, 1915 (Folder 48)
  - Powell, E. Alexander, 1911 (Folder 49)
  - Pratt, E. L., 1927-1929 (Folder 50)
  - Pratt, Julia D., 1916-1918 (Folder 51)
  - Prince, Edward E., 1914 (Folder 52)
  - Princeton Record, 1915 (Folder 53)
  - Pritchett, Henry S., 1910-1917 (Box 77, Folder 1)
  - Progressive National Committee, 1912 (Folder 2)
  - Prohibition Foundation, 1923 (Folder 3)
  - Protzman, Eugene C., 1916-1931 (Folder 4)
  - Prudhommeaux, J., 1913 (Folder 5)
  - Public, 1919 (Folder 6)
  - Pugsley, Fremont L., 1914 (Folder 7)
  - Pulsford, E., 1912-1918 (Folder 8)
  - Pulsifer, William E., 1915 (Folder 9)
  - Purtell, W. H., 1915 (Folder 10)
  - Putnam's Sons, G. P., 1915-1918 (Folder 11)
  - Putnam, George H., 1916-1927 (Folder 12)
  - Putnam, Ruth, 1914 (Folder 13)
  - Race Relations Survey, 1924 (Folder 14)
  - Raker, James E., 1920 (Folder 15)
  - Ramsey, W. H., 1915 (Folder 16)
  - Rand School of Social Science, 1919 (Folder 17)
  - Randall, Charles H., 1920 (Folder 18)
  - Randall, John Herman, 1928 (Folder 19)
  - Rankin, Jeannette, 1917-1918 (Folder 20)
  - Rauschenbusch, Walter, 1916 (Folder 21)
  - Ravenscroft, D. W., 1915 (Folder 22)
  - Raymond, W. P., 1913 (Folder 23)
  - Redfield, C.L., 1900-1902 (Folder 24)
  - Redslob, Robert, 1914 (Folder 25)
  - Reed, Charles Wesley, 1912-1913 (Folder 26)
  - Reed, John W., 1910 (Folder 27)
  - Reed, Verner Z., 1915 (Folder 28)
  - Reese, C. A., 1915 (Folder 29)
  - Reeves, Cora D., 1922 (Folder 30)
  - Reeves, James B., Mrs., 1920 (Folder 31)
  - Reeves, William Pember, 1911 (Folder 32)
  - Reid, Gilbert, 1912-1921 (Folder 33)
  - Reinsch, Paul S., 1922 (Folder 34)
  - Rendtorff, K. G., 1912-1916 (Folder 35)
  - Republic, 1915 (Folder 36)
  - Republican National Committee, 1924 (Folder 37)
  - Rerrick, C. E., 1915 (Folder 38)
  - Rexroth, Heinrich, 1914 (Folder 39)
  - Reynolds, James E., 1917 (Folder 40)
  - Rice, Merton N., 1915 (Folder 41)
  - Richet, Charles, 1910-1928 (Folder 42)
  - Rivière, J. P., 1911-1922 (Folder 43)
  - Robbins, Emily, 1915 (Folder 44)
  - Robbins, Marcus W., 1922 (Folder 45)
  - Roberts, A. J., 1914-1915 (Folder 46)
  - Robinson, Edgar E., 1912-1928 (Folder 47)
  - Robinson, Emily, 1915 (Folder 48)
  - Robinson, Karl D., 1915 (Folder 49)
  - Roeder, Eugen H. A., von, 1911 (Folder 50)
  - Rogers, George W., 1895 (Folder 51)
  - Rogers, R. W., 1915 (Folder 52)
  - Rogers, Robert W., 1918 (Folder 53)
  - Rohner, F., 1914 (Folder 54)
  - Rojas, Luis Manuel, 1918-1928 (Folder 55)
  - Rolph, James, 1912 (Folder 56)
  - Romero, Eduardo, 1917 (Folder 57)
  - Rooseboom, M. P., ca. 1917 (Folder 58)
  - Roosevelt, Theodore, 1901-1917 (Folder 59)
  - Root, Elihu, 1923 (Folder 60)
  - Root, Robert C., 1912-1920 (Folder 61)
  - Rosenthal, E. P., 1915 (Box 78, Folder 1)
  - Rosenthal, Morris, 1914 (Folder 2)
  - Rottcher, Fritz, 1913-1929 (Folder 3)
  - Rowell, Chester H., 1913-1929 (Folder 4)
  - Rowley, Charles, 1914 (Folder 5)
  - Roy, Evelyn Trent, 1917 (Folder 6)
  - Roy, Manabendra Nath, 1917 (Folder 7)
  - Royce, Josiah, 1915 (Folder 8)
  - Ruby, Edward E., 1913 (Folder 9)
  - Rucker, William H., 1923-1929 (Folder 10)
  - Russell, Frank M., 1923 (Folder 11)
  - Russell, I. K., 1923 (Folder 12)
  - Russell, Lindsay, 1913-1915 (Folder 13)
  - Russian Information Bureau, 1919 (Folder 14)
  - Ruyssen, Theodore, 1911-1921 (Folder 15)
  - Saburo, Saito, 1915-1919 (?) (Folder 16)
  - Sacramento Chamber of Commerce, 1914 (Folder 17)
  - Safrastian, A. S., 1914-1915 (Folder 18)
  - Sain, Charles M., 1925-1930 (Folder 19)
  - Sakro (?), J. Allen, 1910 (Folder 20)
  - Saleeby, C. W., 1915-1916 (Folder 21)
  - Samuels, Frederick S., 1914 (Folder 22)
  - San Francisco Bulletin, 1912-1923 (Folder 23)
  - San Francisco Chronicle, 1913-1925 (Folder 24)
  - San Francisco Examiner, 1921-1924 (Folder 25)
  - Sanders, M. S., 1915 (Folder 26)
  - Sanders, W. H., 1924 (Folder 27)
  - Sandoval, A., 1914-1917 (Folder 28)
  - Sa'olotoga, 1902 (Folder 29)
  - Sarasin, Paul, 1914 (Folder 30)
  - Sarolea, Charles, 1913-1915 (Folder 31)
  - Sarton, George, 1914-1917 (Folder 32)
  - Sato, Aimaro, 1916 (Folder 33)
  - Sayeda, Juichi, 1915 (Folder 34)
  - Schaeffle, Ernest, 1916-1929 (Folder 35)
  - Schafer, E. A., 1913 (Folder 36)
  - Schallmayer, W., 1910-1916 (Folder 37)
  - Schellens, R., 1915-1916 (Folder 38)
  - Schiller, F. C. S., 1914 (Folder 39)
  - Schipkowsky, Julius, 1915 (Folder 40)
  - Schlumberger, Jacques, 1913-1921 (Folder 41)
  - Schmidlapp, J.G., 1913-1920 (Folder 42)
  - Schmidt, Peter, 1918 (Folder 43)
  - Schneder, D. B., 1913 (Folder 44)
  - Schoan, August, 1914 (Folder 45)
  - Scholz, Richard, 1920-1921 (Folder 46)
  - Schulte, W.H., 1914 (Folder 47)
  - Schurman, Jacob Gould, 1899-1920 (Folder 48)
  - Schuster, J., 1914 (Folder 49)
  - Schutte, John, 1912 (Folder 50)
  - Schwimmer, Rosika, 1914 (Folder 51)
  - Schwolthaler, Robert, 1913 (Folder 52)
  - Scott, James Brown, 1910-1913 (Folder 53)
  - Scott, Robert, 1914 (Folder 54)
  - Scribner's Sons, 1914 (Folder 55)
  - Scudder, Doremus, 1911 (Box 79, Folder 1)
  - Seale, Alvin, 1914-1915 (Folder 2)
  - Searcy, Charles L., 1911 (Folder 3)
  - Seeck, O., 1910 (Folder 4)
  - Selenka, Margaret, 1917-1921 (Folder 5)
  - Sendai American Community, 1913 (Folder 6)
  - Serbian Relief Committee of America, 1919 (Folder 7)
  - Sewall, May Wright, 1910-1918 (Folder 8)
  - Sharpe, William, 1913-1916 (Folder 9)
  - Sharpless, Isaac, 1915 (Folder 10)
  - Shelly, Rebecca, 1916 (Folder 11)
  - Sherman, Ella Burnes, 1912 (Folder 12)
  - Shibley, George H., 1916 (Folder 13)
  - Shibusawa, E., 1913-1930 (Folder 14)
  - Shiff, Jacob, 1919 (Folder 15)
  - Shimada, Bokusen, 1912 (Folder 16)
  - Shinn, Milicent, 1913 (Folder 17)
  - Shipp, F. B., 1921 (Folder 18)
  - Shores, Robert J., 1915 (Folder 19)
  - Short, W. H., 1915-1921 (Folder 20)
  - Show, A. B., 1912 (Folder 21)
  - Showermann, Grant, 1914-1916 (Folder 22)
  - Sieper, E., 1915 (Folder 23)
  - Sihler, Christian, 1917-1919 (Folder 24)
  - Simon, Bertha, 1913 (Folder 25)
  - Simplified Spelling Society, 1916 (Folder 26)
  - Sinclair, Upton, 1915-1918 (Folder 27)
  - Sindo, Michitaro, 1913 (Folder 28)
  - Singer, Emma Riddle, 1914 (Folder 29)
  - Singer, Isadore, 1914 (Folder 30)
  - Skinner, H. M., 1910 (Folder 31)
  - Skinner, M. M., 1913 (Folder 32)
  - Slayden, Ellen Maury, 1917 (Folder 33)
  - Slayden, James L., 1913-1918 (Folder 34)
  - Slocum, William F., 1916 (Folder 35)
  - Slosson, E. E., 1913 (Folder 36)
  - Smallpage, Lafayette J., 1918 (Folder 37)
  - Smith, Albert, 1913-1915 (Folder 38)
  - Smith, Arthur Harvey, 1914 (Folder 39)
  - Smith, Bolton, 1919 (Folder 40)
  - Smith, E. Percival, 1913 (Folder 41)
  - Smith, Edgar I., 1913 (Folder 42)
  - Smith, Elinor A., 1914 (Folder 43)
  - Smith, Frank O., 1915 (Folder 44)
  - Smith, Gordon (?), 1898 (Folder 45)
  - Smith, Hugh M., 1913 (Folder 46)
  - Smith, Larz A., 1915 (Folder 47)
  - Smith, Roderick H., 1914 (Folder 48)
  - Smith, Ruby G., 1913-1918 (Folder 49)
  - Smith, William B., 1913 (Folder 50)
  - Smithson, Noble, 1912 (Folder 51)
  - Smoot, Reed, 1917-1919 (Folder 52)
  - Snyder, J. L., 1914 (Folder 53)
  - Snyder, Z. X., 1914 (Folder 54)
  - Sofia Press, 1913 (Folder 55)
  - Southern California Peace Society, 1911 (Folder 56)
  - Soyeda, Juichi, 1913-1918 (Folder 57)
  - Spanish American Atheneum, 1913 (Folder 58)
  - Spargo, John, 1920 (Folder 59)
  - Spiller, G., 1914-1916 (Folder 60)
  - Spokesman's Review, 1915 (Folder 61)
  - Spreckels, Rudolph, 1916 (Box 80, Folder 1)
  - Spring-Rice, Cecil, 1916 (Folder 2)
  - Springer, Durand, 1914-1916 (Folder 3)
  - Stackpole, Markham W., 1915 (Folder 4)
  - Stafford, W. V., 1915 (Folder 5)
  - Stanford, Jane Lathrop, 1895-1896 (Folder 6)
  - Stanford, Leland, 1893 (Folder 7)
  - Stanford, Thomas M., 1913-1915 (Folder 8)
  - Stanislawsky, Margaret, 1914 (Folder 9)
  - Stanton, Theodore, 1911-1913 (Folder 10)
  - Starr, Frederick, 1920 (Folder 11)
  - Stead, David G., 1912-1930 (Folder 12)
  - Stead, John, 1914 (Folder 13)
  - Stead, W. T., 1910 (Folder 14)
  - Stebbins, Charles L., 1911 (Folder 15)
  - Stechou, E., 1915 (Folder 16)
  - Steinhart, I., 1912 (Folder 17)
  - Stephens, William D., 1916 (Folder 18)
  - Stevens, Kate, 1913-1917 (Folder 19)
  - Stevenson, D.M., 1914 (Folder 20)
  - Stewart, T. E., Mrs., 1915 (Folder 21)
  - Stillman, John M., 1919-1921 (Folder 22)
  - Stokes, W. E. D., 1910 (Folder 23)
  - Stokes, W. R., 1917-1918 (Folder 24)
  - Stolz, Herbert R., 1913-1925 (Folder 25)
  - Stone, George W., 1912-1916 (Folder 26)
  - Stout, Robert, 1915-1924 (Folder 27)
  - Stow, Vanderlynn, 1915 (Folder 28)
  - Strand Magazine, 1913 (Folder 29)
  - Street, Cyrus H., 1911-1913 (Folder 30)
  - Strong, Daniel B., 1916 (Folder 31)
  - Strong, Sidney, 1919-1930 (Folder 32)
  - Strother, E. F., 1912-1916 (Folder 33)
  - Stuart, Graham H., 1928-1929 (Folder 34)
  - Sturge, Sophia, 1914-1916 (Folder 35)
  - Sulgrave Institution, ca. 1914 (Folder 36)
  - Sullivan, Mark, 1913-1924 (Folder 37)
  - Survey, 1921-1924 (Folder 38)
  - Sutherland, W. A., 1913 (Folder 39)
  - Suzuki, Tomitoro, 1913 (Folder 40)
  - Suzumura, H., 1914 (Folder 41)
  - Swain, Joseph, 1911-1924 (Folder 42)
  - Syracuse Young Men's Hebrew Association, 1911 (Folder 43)
  - Taft, William Howard, 1910-1918 (Folder 44)
  - Tait, Annie Laurie, 1923 (Folder 45)
  - Tait, O. A., 1914-1918 (Folder 46)
  - Takahashi, Y., 1913 (Folder 47)
  - Talbert, Wilford E., 1914 (Folder 48)
  - Talmadge, M., 1913 (Folder 49)
  - Tarbell, Ida M., 1910-1914 (Folder 50)
  - Tatlock, John S.P., 1918 (Folder 51)
  - Tausch, Elizabeth, 1920-1924 (Folder 52)
  - Tavenner, Clyde H., 1915-1916 (Folder 53)
  - Tawney, James A., 1911 (Folder 54)
  - Taylor, Frank J., 1928 (Folder 55)
  - Taylor, George W., 1917 (Folder 56)
  - Taylor, H. G., 1918 (Folder 57)
  - Taylor, Walter A., 1912 (Folder 58)
  - Tennessee Law and Order League, 1919 (Folder 59)
  - Tercer Congreso Cientifico Pan-Americano, 1924 (Folder 60)
  - Terman, Lewis M., 1912-1924 (Folder 61)
  - Terzieff, Elizabeth R., 1915-1924 (Folder 62)
  - Thacher, Sherman D., 1914 (Box 81, Folder 1)
  - Thilmont, C., 1915 (Folder 2)
  - Thomas, Anna B., 1915 (Folder 3)
  - Thomas, Augustus O., 1924-1930 (Folder 4)
  - Thomas, Calvin, 1914 (Folder 5)
  - Thomas, Harrison M., 1916 (Folder 6)
  - Thomas, Herbert I., 1910 (Folder 7)
  - Thompson, H. E., Mrs., 1915 (Folder 8)
  - Thompson, H. E., 1917 (Folder 9)
  - Thompson, Herbert, n.d. (Folder 10)
  - Thompson, W. O., 1915 (Folder 11)
  - Thomson, John Stuart, 1913 (Folder 12)
  - Thomson, Robert, 1915 (Folder 13)
  - Thwing, Charles F., 1901-1928 (Folder 14)
  - Thwing, Eugene, 1915-1916 (Folder 15)
  - Tory, J. H., 1915-1918 (Folder 16)
  - Treat, Payson, 1912-1925 (Folder 17)
  - Trevoy, Wilmot V., 1914 (Folder 18)
  - Trotter, Reginald G., 1920 (Folder 19)
  - True, Clara, 1919-1923 (Folder 20)
  - Trueblood, Benjamin F., 1912-1915 (Folder 21)
  - Tryon, James L., 1911-1916 (Folder 22)
  - Turner, Frederick Jackson, 1917 (Folder 23)
  - Turner, George W., 1918 (Folder 24)
  - Turner, Horace K., 1915 (Folder 25)
  - Umano, 1915-1916 (Folder 26)
  - Umfrid, O., 1914 (Folder 27)
  - Underwood, Oscar W., 1912 (Folder 28)
  - Union Interparlementaire, 1912-1915 (Folder 29)
  - United States. Department of Agriculture, 1920 (Folder 30)
  - United States. Department of Justice, 1920-1921 (Folder 31)
  - United States. Department of Labor, 1919-1925 (Folder 32)
  - United States. Department of the Interior, 1900-1925 (Folder 33)
  - United States. Department of the Treasury, 1919-1925 (Folder 34)
  - United States Commission on the Limitation of Armaments, 1910 (Folder 35)
  - Unity, 1923 (Folder 36)
  - Universal Society of Social Improvement, 1918 (Folder 37)
  - Unwin, T. Fisher, 1912-1929 (Folder 38)
  - Usher, Roland G., 1912-1913 (Folder 39)
  - Valentine, John J., 1898-1899 (Folder 40)
  - Van Auken, M. W., 1918 (Folder 41)
  - Van Laer, A. J. F., 1914 (Folder 42)
  - Vaughn, John H., 1912 (Folder 43)
  - "Veritas", 1914 (Folder 44)
  - Vestal, S. C., 1924 (Folder 45)
  - Viand, Marcel, 1913 (Folder 46)
  - Viereck, George S., 1914-1919 (Folder 47)
  - Villard, Fannie Garrison, 1924 (Folder 48)
  - Villard, Oswald Garrison, 1914-1928 (Folder 49)
  - Vogeler, Henry, 1916 (Folder 50)
  - Vogelgesang, C. T., 1923 (Folder 51)
  - Volstead, Andrew, 1920-1922 (Folder 52)
  - Voluntary Parenthood League, Inc., 1924 (Folder 53)
  - Von Boos, Eugenia H., 1913 (Folder 54)
  - Wade, Jeannette H., 1914 (Folder 55)
  - Wadsworth, James W., Jr., 1924 (Folder 56)
  - Wainwright, Richard, 1913 (Folder 57)
  - Wakeman, Elbert, 1915 (Folder 58)
  - Walcott, C. A., 1916 (Folder 59)
  - Wald, Lillian D., 1917 (Folder 60)
  - Wales, Julia Grace, 1917-1923 (Folder 61)
  - Walker, George, 1917 (Folder 62)
  - Walker, John Brisben, 1912 (Folder 63)
  - Walker, T. B., 1914 (Folder 64)
  - Wallas, Graham, 1914-1916 (Folder 65)
  - Walling, William English, 1928 (Folder 66)
  - Walsh, David I., 1924 (Box 82, Folder 1)
  - Walsh, Walter, 1911-1920 (Folder 2)
  - Walter, Caroline, 1915 (Folder 3)
  - Walton, John Whittlesey, 1912 (Folder 4)
  - War and Peace, 1913-1918 (Folder 5)
  - War Trade Board, 1918 (Folder 6)
  - Ward, Robert DeC., 1922 (Folder 7)
  - Warden, A. A., 1915-1922 (Folder 8)
  - Warner, Charles Dudley, 1898 (Folder 9)
  - Warner, John Dewitt, 1914-1915 (Folder 10)
  - Watanabe, Y., 1911 (Folder 11)
  - Waylen, Hector, 1913-1916 (Folder 12)
  - Weardale, Lord, 1910 (Folder 13)
  - Weber, Max, 1919 (Folder 14)
  - Webster, Allen, 1914 (Folder 15)
  - Webster, Francis, 1916-1923 (Folder 16)
  - Webster, R. Valentine, 1916 (Folder 17)
  - Weeks, George F., 1916-1924 (Folder 18)
  - Weinstock, Harris, 1912 (Folder 19)
  - Welling, Richard, 1914 (Folder 20)
  - Wells, J. W., 1921-1927 (Folder 21)
  - Welsh, Charles, 1910 (Folder 22)
  - Welsh, Herbert, 1915 (Folder 23)
  - Welton, Harold, 1911 (Folder 24)
  - Wendte, Charles W., 1918-1928 (Folder 25)
  - Werner, Max, 1914 (Folder 26)
  - West, Clara L., 1914-1915 (Folder 27)
  - West, F. W., 1912 (Folder 28)
  - West, James E., 1915 (Folder 29)
  - Westbrook, F. F., 1915 (Folder 30)
  - Wetzel, William A., 1910 (Folder 31)
  - Wheeler, Benjamin I., 1911-1918 (Folder 32)
  - Whitaker, Herman, 1917 (Folder 33)
  - Whitaker, Robert, 1915-1919 (Folder 34)
  - Whitcomb, C. T. C., 1912 (Folder 35)
  - White, Andrew D., 1903-1916 (Folder 36)
  - White, C., 1916 (Folder 37)
  - White, Fred D., 1899 (Folder 38)
  - White, Horace, 1913 (Folder 39)
  - White, William Allen, 1915-1928 (Folder 40)
  - Whiteley, James G., 1915 (Folder 41)
  - Whitman, Charles S., 1917 (Folder 42)